<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top Cities</string>

    <string name="bangkok_info">Bangkok, the capital of Thailand, is the most visited city in the world thanks to a whopping 22 million international visitors!\n\nWreathed in the noise of tuk-tuks and constant activity is the city of Bangkok, where map-less exploration always leads to fun discovery.\n\nEnjoy the usual city comforts of megamalls and modern spaces before turning towards its collection of golden temples and shrines. Follow your nose to Bangkok\’s countless street markets stuffed with spicy, sour, sweet, and salty flavors, then hop on a boat to reach their floating markets.\n\nIn the night, Chinatown and Sukhumvit reveals a vibrant nightlife that is both cosmopolitan and cultural. And to forget to enjoy the exciting day-trips away from this busy city!\n\nBut learn how to stay safe in Bangkok before you go, and I also suggest that you take a look at one of the following travel guides. They are both excellent and worth reading.</string>

    <string name="paris_info">Paris is the second most visited city in the world and the most visited city in Europe!\n\nParis will arrest your attention with its classic buildings, arching Parisian bridges and elegant boulevards.\n\nTake a cruise along River Seine for a quick look at the city\’s historical monuments, or swing by individual neighborhoods for Eiffel Tower, Notre Dame, the Louvre, and more.\n\nAnd as an established art and fashion capital, visitors can\’t go without seeing the collections of Musee d\’Orsay and Centre Pompidou. Atmospheric bookstores, vintage shops and flea markets make their mark beside art nouveau department stores such as Galeries Lafayette.\n\nTo immerse yourself in this beautiful city from the comfort of your couch, pick any of the following photo book. They all include breathtaking photos that will surprise and delight you for sure!</string>

    <string name="london_info">London is clearly one of the most popular cities in the world! The gothic architecture in London is matched by splashes of innovation (such as the Shard, Tate Modern, and the Sky Garden), offering up grand and historical quarters.\n\nYou\’ll be charmed by the taverns and all of West End and impressed by London\’s contemporary art, theater and literature.\n\nGreeting you with both the beauty of green parks and urban sprawl, the city will take you through a stunning historical journey.</string>

    <string name="dubai_info">Dubai rises out from the desert in all its futuristic glory.\n\nHigh-rises dominate the skyline, housing mega-malls, and sleek office blocks.\n\nCity life is defined by lazy shopping, performance venues, serene places of worship, and fancy rooftop terraces.\n\nOn the fringes are beaches, pieces of nature in contrast to the man-made aquariums and botanical gardens.\n\nAnd of course, you can sign up for a desert trip and experience riding a camel, or flying down the dunes on a four-wheeler.</string>

    <string name="singapore_info">Green and innovative, Singapore is a city designed with the future in mind.\n\nHop from attraction to another with its efficient transportation system and hit up the diverse neighborhoods of Little India to Chinatown.\n\nFrom hawker centers to street markets to fine dining, you\’ll be eating your fill of multi-national cuisine – Singapore is a foodie must-visit.\n\nWhen you\’re not busy eating, you will be basking in the luxe Orchard Road shopping mall, or exploring the famous Botanic Gardens.</string>

    <string name="kuala_lumpur">Open your senses to absorb Kuala Lumpur\’s lively energy!\n\nThanks to its multicultural mix of Malay, Chinese, and Indian community, the city is home to mosques and temples that stand out from gleaming skyscrapers.\n\nThis celebration of historical and modern also shows itself in the contrasting high-fashion shopping malls and vibrant street markets.\n\nSpend your holiday scouting out designer brands and hunting down the best hawker stalls for the best of two worlds.</string>

    <string name="new_york">New York, or the city where dreams are made!\n\nFollowing the city\’s grid-like design, trawl the streets for private art galleries and world-famous the Met, MoMA, and Guggenhiem. Indie bookstores, brightly lit Chinatown, high-end boutiques and hipster cafés lead into grand office buildings and huge Central Park.\n\nEnjoy lavish performances in Broadway or eat your way through rooftop restaurants and hole-in-the-wall eateries. New York is THE metropolitan city that will get you buzzing in excitement.</string>

    <string name="istanbul">Istanbul is a historical trove, its strategic location having witnessed many ruling empires.\n\nTracing back to the Greeks, Romans, Venetians, and finally the Ottomans, the city is adorned with Byzantine churches and imperial mosques.\n\nRecent decades have seen sharp spikes in the skyline as galleries, museums, and tall office towers grew alongside the old.\n\nVisitors also praise Istanbul’s culinary diversity which is a mix of Asian and European flavor; but local kebab and mezze is the go-to.</string>

    <string name="tokyo">If there was a city that lived in the future, Tokyo is it!\n\nClean streets, chrome skyscrapers, and ever-moving crowds keep Tokyo running 24/7.\n\nSmart electronics and convenient technology set incredibly high living standards.\n\nYet amidst the neon signboards and flashy urban sprawl are pockets of green and the spiritual; Tokyo remembers its past deeply. Visit the Edo-styled streets of Yanezen and serene Meiji Shrine.\n\nTo experience Tokyo, look past the trendy cafés and bold fashions to find under-the-tracks eateries, languid neighborhoods, and hidden shrines.</string>

    <string name="antalya">Set out for the stunning Antalya, a stylish city poised along the Turkish Riviera.\n\nCombining the Mediterranean coastline with preserved Kaleici old quarters, Antalya is a romantic getaway.\n\nStroll through the city for finely restored Ottoman houses and wind up at the harbor.\n\nWith the scent of the sea in mind, explore the Suna and Inan Kirac Kaleici Museum or Antalya Museum for a walk down memory lane.</string>

    <string name="seoul">Seoul constantly upgrades with new trends – in fact, it is the trending holiday destination.\n\nThe city is a youth-driven hub, luring in K-pop fans, and fashion gurus with promises of cultural activities, idol sightings, and shopping.\n\nBut don’t just spend your time browsing the shops and feasting on midnight snacks; Seoul has plenty of heritage sites for you to see.\n\nSight-see its palaces in traditional hanbok and delve into dated markets for another piece of the puzzle.</string>

    <string name="osaka">If you don’t dig the fast-paced Tokyo, hit up the friendly and sun-warmed Osaka instead.\n\nThe gateway to Kyoto and Kobe, Osaka is a cultural center that delights with both heritage sites and commercial fun.\n\nEnergetic Dotonbori is never empty of people, comprised of restaurants that range from okonomiyaki to standing ramen stalls.\n\nAdjacent Shinsaibashi is kilometers of boutiques, bookstores and sweet shops; shopping malls are concentrated in Umeda.\n\nOsaka Castle and Tennoji Temple are two of many historical structures, and Universal Studios Japan is a full-day distraction!</string>

    <string name="makkah">Highly symbolic Makkah is a key pilgrimage destination for all Muslims.\n\nThe city where Prophet Muhammad (pbuh) was born, Makkah is a religious center with sacred Kaaba at its heart – it is Islam’s holiest city.\n\nOnly Muslims are allowed into this desert valley city, which dates back to 7th century.\n\nVisitors (by millions per year) will find that Makkah is developed, modern buildings surrounding the religious hotspot; in contrast, cozy homes are nestled in rocky hills to reflect its traditional nature.</string>

    <string name="phuket">Phuket is beach bliss and karst islands, encompassing two national parks and too many islands to explore.\n\nThe range of beaches is spectacular, from part-central Patong to luxurious Surin and Ao Bang Thao. Meanwhile, stunning coral reefs invite scuba divers and snorkeling groups to explore the glittering waters of the Similan Islands.\n\nYou can also kayak into Ao Phang-Nga’s lagoons and wind around limestone karsts.\n\nPhuket Town also offers museums, cooking classes, Chinese shrines, and wildlife sanctuaries to keep things fresh.</string>

    <string name="pattaya">If it is heat you want, hit up touristy Pattaya for endless beach fun and a party-themed central area.\n\nThere are of course, Thailand’s stunning temples and shrines, but Pattaya is known for its seaside resorts.\n\nSign up for a harried tour of the city before settling in along the coast for more sun and relaxation. This is a city that embraces hedonist attitudes to the max.</string>

    <string name="milan">Elegant Milan is all about creativity and the arts.\n\nBreaking free of Italian wars to pave way for post-war development, Milan impresses with art deco and futuristic architecture.\n\nIts main draw however, remains in its art and fashion.\n\nMarvel at the city’s art collection and strike up conversation with gallery owners; Triennale design museum will wow you.\n\nStop by fashion houses, showrooms, boutiques and all the stylish spaces you can think of.\n\nTo round off, indulge in the rich and Mediterranean-influenced Milanese cooking.</string>

    <string name="barcelona">Barcelona is generous with its fresh sea bounty and world-class architecture.\n\nYou can expect as many flavors of architecture as there are tapas – too many to see in a week.\n\nFrom Roman-era subterranean spaces to the Gothic Quarter of the Middle Ages, to Gaudi’s modernism masterpieces, the city is dotted with magnificent architecture.\n\nSandy beaches, rolling Collserola hills, majestic Montjuic and sculpture gardens add to the picturesque layout. With endless museums, galleries, taverns and green spaces to visit, you’ll be on your feet from day to night.</string>

    <string name="palma">Spain’s Palma De Mallorca has witnessed its share of rulers.\n\nFrom 13th century Christian leaders to the preceding Moors and Romans, this historical chain of empires are seen in the city’s mixed architecture and historical sites.\n\nStart with the Gothic Catedral and branch out into the medieval streets.\n\nYou’ll see lively public squares, noble townhouses, imposing baroque churches and colorful street markets.\n\nThe bohemian vibe is also strong in suburban neighborhoods, teeming with craft studios and galleries.\n\nBy the main reason why people visit Mallorca are its famous cristal clear beaches!\n\nFrom Alcudia to Cala d’or, you’ll find plenty of wonderful spot where you can relax and swim with the fishes (literally) in the Mediterranean sea.</string>

    <string name="bali">Another trending location that has taken over social media feeds, especially Instagram, is Bali, featuring lush jungles and seaside villas. These recent years, it’s beauty made Bali one of the most popular tourist destinations!\n\nTraditions reign as locals march to temple ceremonies and hosts incredible dance performances; the island celebrates the spiritual with colorful displays.\n\nBali is also diverse – you can treat yourself at lavish Bukit Peninsula, explore the mysterious Ubud or party hard at Kuta.\n\nDiving sites, ancient monuments, city comforts, and seaside retreat in one, Bali is potential!\n\nAs millennials would say, “it is a mood”!</string>

    <string name="hong_kong">The harbor might not be as fragrant as its name proclaims, but Hong Kong’s busy streets and sky-high buildings will linger in your senses!\n\nThe city’s skyline hides much of its unique cultural-scape, international brands and sleek malls existing beside haggling vendors and garish goods.\n\nThere’s always something to see or do, whether it is taking a ferry across the harbor or snapping panoramic shots on Victoria Peak.\n\nFill your itinerary with dimsum eats and temples visits. Enjoy retail time and water-themed Ocean Park. Treat yourself to challenging hikes and spellbinding coastal views for Hong Kong is more than concrete and steel.</string>
</resources>